https://totalsignco.com.au/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
––
PERTH'S COMPLETE SIGN SERVICE.
Privacy Policy
We understand the importance of protecting your right to privacy and have therefore prepared this statement to help you understand how we aim to protect the privacy of your personal information.
In this document we outline what details we may keep about you and why we need these details.
The new Privacy Amendment (Private Sector) Act 2000 amends the Privacy Act (from 21 December 2001) to include laws that regulate the way private organisations handle personal information.
The Act contains 10 National Privacy Principles that regulate, among other things, how organisations collect, store and protect the quality of personal information. Also, how these organisations should use and share personal information with other organisations. The National Privacy Principles form part of all our procedures and policies and the way personal information and details are administered.
What personal information will we keep about you?
The type of personal information we collect about you may include your name, address, date of birth, telephone number, fax number, email address, company and/or business information and other details.
Risks of using the Internet
You should note that there are security risks in transmitting information via the internet. You should assess these potential risks when deciding whether to use our on-line services. If you do not wish to transmit information via e-mail or this website, there are other ways in which you can provide this information, such as by mail or telephone.
Collection of browsing information
If you visit our site to read or download information, such as news stories or articles, much of the information we do collect is statistical only (e.g., the domain from which you access the Internet, the date and time you access our site, and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site) and not personally identifiable. We use this information about the number of visitors and their use of the sites in aggregate form to make our site more useful and attractive to you.
We will only record your e-mail address if you send us a message. It will not be added to a mailing list without your knowledge or permission.
Why do we need your personal information?
The personal information you provide to us will be retained only for as long as necessary to meet the purpose for which the information was collected or as required by law. We do not share personal information with third parties except as necessary to carry out our business or as required by law or other legal processes. We never sell your personal information.
Can I see the personal information held about me?
Under the National Privacy Principles, you have a right to know what information we hold about you, and you are entitled to see this information to ensure it is correct. To obtain this information, please contact us to ask them for your personal details. The Privacy Act gives limited circumstances in which some or all access to this information may be denied. If this applies to you, we will explain this to you when you ask for your information.
Credit card information
Credit card details provided either electronically or over the telephone will never be kept on file. Once the charge has been processed the credit card details are destroyed.
How can I contact Total Sign Co?
If you want further information on how we handle personal information, or if you want to complain about a possible breach of privacy, please contact us in one of the following ways:
Mail:
